Andy Sze

Owner, Fastraxx Group and Logistics and Supply Chain Consultant

Greater Chicago Area

Logistics and Supply Chain

1. Fastraxx Group

Current

2. , Galesburg Regional Economic Development Association

Previous

1. Clipper Group

1. MBA, Executive Program (XP 47) at The University of Chicago - Booth

Education

School of Business

15 connections

Connect

Send InMail

More options

• www.linkedin.com/pub/andy-sze/0/56/5b

Summary

Andy Sze is the Founder of Fastraxx Group, a logistics consultancy with strong Asian expertise and government contacts. He is currently the Transportation and Logistics Specialist for Asian Development Bank's Central Asia Transport Sector Strategy Study. Mr. Sze has more than 30 years of senior management experience in global transportation and logistics. He was the CEO of a highly successful intermodal logistics company sold for 11 times EBITDA and 6 times book. Mr. Sze holds BS in Industrial & Systems Engineering from Illinois Institute of Technology, MBA from University of Chicago, and MS & ABD in Industrial Engineering & Management Science from Northwestern University. He is a Fellow of the Intermodal Transportation Institute and a former Director of American Society of Transportation & Logistics. Mr. Sze serves on the Business Advisory Council (Executive Committee) of The Transportation Center, Northwestern University and the BAC of College of Business, University of Illinois.

Specialties

Multimodal transportation, logistics, freight forwarding, intermodal markeing, supply chain management, trade facilitation, transport facilitation, mergers & acquisition due diligence studies, doing business in China

Experience

Owner

Fastraxx Group

Currently holds this position

Senior Advisor

Galesburg Regional Economic Development Association

2006 – Present (6 years)

President & CEO, Partner

Clipper Group

Privately Held; 201-500 employees; Maritime industry

September 1983 – August 1999 (16 years)

Mr. Sze led Clipper's expansion into the high margin cold chain logistics and high growth intermodal logistics businesses. He transformed Clipper from a traditional asset and labor intensive, unionized transportation company into an asset and labor light, non-union logistics company.

After consistently achieved over 50% ROE, Mr. Sze orchestrated the sale of Clipper for 11 times EBITDA and 6 times book to a major transport holding company.

Education

The University of Chicago - Booth School of Business

MBA, Executive Program (XP 47)

1980 - 1982

Northwestern University

MS, ABD, Industrial & Systems Engineering

1973 - 1976

Illinois Institute of Technology

BS (High Honors), Industrial & Systems Engineering

1970 - 1973

Activities and Societies: Tau Beta Pi